{
    "questions":[
  {
    "question": "What is JSON?",
    "answers": [
      "website",
      "a popular means of transferring data between servers and clients",
      "Journalistic Stream Of News",
      "teacher name"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "2",
    "level": 0,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u0027Singleton\u0027?",
    "answers": [
      "Common name for Non-functional requirements",
      "a software design pattern that restricts the instantiation of a class to one object",
      "a software design pattern that restricts the instantiation of a class to limited number of object",
      "Common name for Domain requirements"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "3",
    "level": 1,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "test driven developments includes?",
    "answers": [
      "Software Testing",
      "Regression Testing",
      "Maintenance Testing",
      "Code Testing"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "2",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "\u0027Factory method\u0027, \u0027Strategy\u0027 and \u0027Adapter\u0027 are 3 kinds of:",
    "answers": [
      "Cloud srevices",
      "functional Requirements",
      "agile methods",
      "Design Patterns"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "In testing process: what comes first?",
    "answers": [
      "Release testing",
      "Development",
      "User testing"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "2",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tools that used for unit testing?",
    "answers": [
      "draw.io",
      "JUnit",
      "Xampp",
      "Visual Paradigm"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "1",
    "level": 0,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "before you release your product to  real use she needs to pass the tests of",
    "answers": [
      "Software Testing",
      "Release Testing",
      "Maintenance Testing",
      "Code Testing"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "2",
    "level": 0,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a \u0027Private cloud\u0027 advantage?",
    "answers": [
      "High level of security",
      "Customizable ",
      "High performance",
      "Low cost"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "\u0027Windows Azure\u0027, \u0027Heruko\u0027 and \u0027force.com\u0027 are examples for:",
    "answers": [
      "IaaS",
      "SaaS ",
      "PaaS",
      "BaaS"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "3",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "tool for version control is?",
    "answers": [
      "big bucket",
      "Turrent",
      "visual paradigm",
      "draw.io"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "1",
    "level": 0,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a feature of a good software?",
    "answers": [
      "stand alone system",
      "entertainment",
      "effiency",
      "have a nice font"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "3",
    "level": 2,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following roles is not described as a core role in \u0027Scrum\u0027?",
    "answers": [
      "Product owner",
      "Team",
      "Product owner",
      "architect"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": 1,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "UML Diagrams types includes one of the following diagrams:",
    "answers": [
      "Petri Net",
      "BPMN",
      "DSD",
      "StateChart"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": 1,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "question": "UML Diagrams types includes one of the following diagrams:",
    "answers": [
      "Petri Net",
      "BPMN",
      "DSD",
      "StateChart"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": 1,
    "team": "hedgehog"
  }
]}